<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on michael s.</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on michael s.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 10:16:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social Medium</title>
      <link>/posts/social-medium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 10:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/social-medium/</guid>
      <description>Stats Are Not My Friend Part of the motivation for me to start writing posts here under my own space is down to two things:
 I can have more control over what I post and how it looks I don&amp;rsquo;t have any analytics  Sure, it&amp;rsquo;s more complicated and time consuming to create, edit and publish new words here, and Medium.com gives me a really nice user experience to write in, but point #2 is the most pertinent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abusing Dictionaries in Swift in Six Simple Examples</title>
      <link>/posts/dictionary-abuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dictionary-abuse/</guid>
      <description>Example One: Simple The dictionary! A simple concept - thing has a key and a value and you use one to extract the other. Like how when you were younger, you&amp;rsquo;d use a dictionary to extract all of the swear words.
Developers use them all the time because they&amp;rsquo;re simple to understand, flexible and consistent in their behaviour.
If you&amp;rsquo;re not too familiar with dictionaries though, here&amp;rsquo;s a simple example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timing Is Everything</title>
      <link>/posts/timing-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 21:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/timing-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>And I guess the question is &amp;ldquo;Why now?&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;ve been loathe to start one of these things for a number of reasons and they normally fall into this order:
 What do I really have to say? Why would anyone care what I have to say? What if people don&amp;rsquo;t like/care about what I have to say? Can I be bothered to go through the effort of making a website?  The answer to the first question is a very succinct &amp;ldquo;not a huge amount&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
